{
    "type": "module",
    "Lesson 0": [
        {
            "question": "What is this course about?",
            "answer": "Learning python",
            "options": [
                "Making Videos",
                "Playing flappy bird",
                "None of the other options"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What are some descriptions of python?",
            "answer": "All of the other options",
            "options": [
                "It uses text",
                "It has rules about how you write it",
                "It is used to make programs"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 1": [
        {
            "question": "How would you print \"Majulah Singapura!\"",
            "answer": "print(\"Majulah Singapura!\")",
            "options": [
                "print(Majulah Singapura!)",
                "print(\"Majulah Singapura\")",
                "None of the other options"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the syntax for writing comments?",
            "answer": "#",
            "options": [
                "-",
                "\"\"",
                "comment()"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 2": [
        {
            "question": "What are data types?",
            "answer": "They are categories (types) that you store data in",
            "options": [
                "They are words that we print to the console",
                "They are text boxes for the user to input",
                "They are boxes that you push around"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the datatype of this: 0.25",
            "answer": "Float",
            "options": [
                "String",
                "Integer",
                "Boolean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the data type of this: \"True\" ",
            "answer": "String",
            "options": [
                "Integer",
                "Float",
                "Boolean"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 3": [
        {
            "question": "What is the value of number? <p>number = int(161.803)</p>",
            "answer": "161",
            "options": [
                "161.8",
                "162",
                "161.803"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>myVariable = 25 \nmyVariable = \"timmy\" \nmyVariable = 10 \nmyVariable = \"10\" </p>What is the value of myVariable at the end?",
            "answer": "\"10\"",
            "options": [
                "25",
                "\"timmy\"",
                "10"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>chocolate = input(\"How many chocolates are there?\") \ncherries = chocolate \nchocolate = 256 \nprint(chocolate) </p>What prints at the end?",
            "answer": "\"256\"",
            "options": [
                "\"How many chocolates are there?\"",
                "\"cherries\"",
                "It depends on what the user put in"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 4": [
        {
            "question": "What is the value of number? <p>number = 98 - 10 * (3+2) / 8</p>",
            "answer": "91.75",
            "options": [
                "29.5",
                "6",
                "55"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>num = 200 \nnum += 50 \nnum *= 4 \nnum /= 100 \nnum -= 5 \nprint(num) </p>What is printed?",
            "answer": "5",
            "options": [
                "1000",
                "250",
                "10"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>a = int(input(\"put in a number\")) \na -= 5 \nb = 100 \nb += a </p> What is the value of b in the end?",
            "answer": "95 more than what the user put in",
            "options": [
                "100",
                "100 more than what the user put in",
                "5"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 5": [
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>home = False \nif home == True: \n &emsp;print(\"At home\") \n else if home == False: \n &emsp;print(\"Not at home\") </p>What prints out?",
            "answer": "It gives an error",
            "options": [
                "Nothing prints out",
                "\"At home\"",
                "\"Not at home\""
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p>cookies = 10 \ncookies += 5 \ncookies -=7 \nif cookies == 0: \n &emsp;print(\"There are no cookies\") \nelif cookies == 7: \n &emsp;print(\"There are 7 cookies\") \nelse: \n&emsp;print(\"There are neither 7 nor 0 cookies\") </p>What prints out?",
            "answer": "\"There are neither 7 nor 0 cookies\"",
            "options": [
                "\"There are no cookies\"",
                "\"There are 7 cookies\"",
                "Nothing prints out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code has an error. What is it? <p>color = 'blue' \nif color == \"red\" \n &emsp;print(\"Color is red\") \nelif color == \"blue\": \n &emsp;print(\"Color is blue\") </p>",
            "answer": "Missing colon : after \"red\" at line 2",
            "options": [
                "Single quotation marks ' when declaring color at line 1",
                "Double equals sign == at line 2 and line 4",
                "There is a tab (4 spaces) before the print statements at line 3 and 5"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 6": [
        {
            "question": "What prints out? <p>print(120 / 6 < 20) </p>",
            "answer": "\"False\"",
            "options": [
                "\"True\"",
                "\"true\"",
                "\"false\""
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p> day = \"Monday\" \nif day == \"Saturday\" or day == \"Sunday\": \n &emsp;print(\"It's the weekend!\") \nelse: \n &emsp;print(\"It's a weekday.\") </p>What prints out?",
            "answer": "\"It's a weekday.\"",
            "options": [
                "\"It's the weekend!\"",
                "A type error occurs",
                "A value error occurs"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The following code is run: <p> roomA = 10 \nroomB = 15 \nroomA += 3 \nroomB -= 5 \nif roomA < roomB: \n &emsp;print(\"Room A has\" + (roomB - roomA) + \" less people than room B\") \nelif roomA > roomB: \n &emsp;print(\"Room A has\" + (roomA - roomB) + \" more people than room B\")",
            "answer": "Room A has 3 more people than room B",
            "options": [
                "Room A has 2 more people than room B",
                "Room A has 3 less people than room B",
                "Room A has 2 less people than room B"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 7": [
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 8": [
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 9": [
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Lesson 10": [
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "ans",
            "options": [
                "option0",
                "option1",
                "option2"
            ]
        }
    ]
}